

Bi Landry-Ange

Software Engineer

H

Langages: French - English



France



+33 0776031636



http://gnango.com



me@gnango.com

About me ———

Software Engineer who worked at different environment around the world such as public sector, startup, big company and consultancy and passionate about craftmanship, best pratices and software architecture. Problem solver, good teammates i'm able to apply new technology in real world project in time. In other hand i'm passionate about traveling, music, discover new culture and make friends around the world.

Skills ———

Python 3*

Serverless

FastAPI

Design Pattern

Database

API Gateway

Microservice

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Interests

Enthusiast to learn new technology for real project, like to take up challenges in industry 4.0.

Strenghts

Problem Solver. Team Player. Great Analytical Skills.

Technical Skills

Paradigm Fonctional Programming, Object Oriented Programming.

WebService RESTFull, GraphQL, webRTC, RabbitMQ, SocketIO, Celery.

Database PostgreSQL, Redis, MongoDB, ElasticSearch.

Versioning Git, Github, GitLab.

Tools Sphinx, Black, mypy, Poetry, Cookiecutter, Buildout.

Cloud Docker, Kubernetes, AWS (lambda, s3, route 53, dynamo...)

Framework DRF, Pyramid Web framework, FastAPI.

Work Experiences

Paris Python Backend Developer at ADAY Since July 2021

Designed and architectured web services

Paris Software Engineer at LANSROD Oct 2019-Apr 2021

Design audit scoring framework: NATIXIS

Hanoi System Developer at VNEDUTECH Nov 2018 - Oct 2019

Design a RTC platform for educational field based on webRTC

Abidjan Software Engineer at FFPSU May 2016 - Dec 2017

Design and maintain an applicative intranet

Abidjan Web Developer at MAGNACORP Jan 2015 - Mar 2016

Design website and web application to manage palm oil unit.

Education

2018 Master Degree VNU/IFI - Hanoi

Intelligent System and Multimedia.

2015 Master Degree Edhec Group - Abidjan

Software Engineering.

2013 Bachelor Degree Edhec Group - Abidjan

Software Engineering.

2011 Associate Degree HEC La Roche - Abidjan

Computer Science.

Personal Projects

Gnango in Progress

Gnango is a real-time communication platform for educational fields on top of Information Technologies and Artificial intelligence.

Recommender System Research

State of art and proposal to solve Recommender System Cold Start Problem using demographic data.